

#### Personal

Indio, California Location

(909)-205-6607 Phone

hola@godiego.me

**(** https://www.godiego.me/

### Languages

English \*\*\* Spanish

### Skills

French

Bootstrap 3/4 Javascript jQuery AngularJS ASP.NET MVC Firebase Git ReactJS SQL **★★☆☆☆** NodeJS ★★☆☆☆ C#

Full list of skills can be found on my website

# Diego Bernal

Web Developer

Software developer with an engineering background, specializing in web technologies. Possesses strong problem-solving skills and an affinity for clean, maintainable, readable and reusable code and best practices. Experienced in developing static websites and complex, multi-layer web applications.

# Experience

## Readylink Healthcare

June 2014 - Present

Web Developer

- Designed and developed ASP .NET MVC application with Bootstrap 3, jQuery, SQL and C#
- Designed and developed Single Page Application with AngularJS
- Developed build scripts to bundle and minify SPA for production with Gulp
- Provided test coverage for software through unit, end-to-end, and integration testing.

# Freelance Developer

2016 - Present

A list of my work can be found on my website at https://www.godiego.me/portfolio

- Build, manage, deploy web projects specified by clients
- Mostly static websites built with Jekyll and Bootstrap 4

# Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering CSU San Bernardino	Sept 2009 - June 2014
Minor in Applied Physics CSU San Bernardino	Sept 2009 - June 2014
Minor in Mathematics CSU San Bernardino	Sept 2009 - June 2014